A Guide to the Papers of James J. Kilpatrick
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: Editorials and Editorial Materials
  - 1956 Right of Interposition (Box-folder 62:1)
  - 1956-1958 Twentieth Precinct Society (Box-folder 62:2)
  - 1957U.S. News-Article Letters (Box-folder 62:3)
- Series III: Speeches and Public Appearances
  - 1960 Nov 8-28 Debate-"The Nation's Future" v. Dr. Martin Luther King Jr.-Responses-Pro (Box-folder 62:4)
  - 1960 Nov 29-Dec 21 Debate-"The Nation's Future" v. Dr. Martin Luther King Jr.-Responses - Pro (Box-folder 62:5)
  - 1960-1961 King Debate - Con (Box-folder 62:6)
  - 1960 Mar-Apr "Open End" Show - Television-April 1960 (Box-folder 62:7)
  - 1960 May-Jul "Open End" Show - Television-April 1960 (Box-folder 63:1)
  - 1960 Aug-Sep "Open End" Show - Television-April 1960 (Box-folder 63:2)
  - 1959-1960 Speeches (Box-folder 63:3)
  - 1964-1965 Speeches-1965 (Box-folder 63:4)
  - 1962 Speeches-Fan District Rally (Box-folder 63:5)
  - 1965 Speeches-Florida, February 4-5, 1965 (Box-folder 63:6)
  - 1961 Speeches-Georgia-February 16, 1961 (Box-folder 63:7)
  - 1962 Speeches-Indianapolis-Society of Individualists (Box-folder 63:8)
  - 1964 Speeches-Invitations Declined (Box-folder 63:9)
  - 1964-1965 Speeches-Invitations Declined (Box-folder 63:10)
  - 1965 Speeches-Invitations Declined (Box-folder 63:11)
  - 1964 Speeches-(Unconfirmed) Invitations (Box-folder 64:1)
  - 1964 Speeches-Minor Local Talks (Box-folder 64:2)
  - 1957-1965 Speeches-Miscellaneous Speeches and Essays (Box-folder 64:3)
  - 1964 Speeches-Reaction (Box-folder 64:4)
  - 1963 Speeches-"Reflections of a Sunday/View from a Southern Exposure" (Box-folder 64:5)
  - 1962-1963 Television-CBS Press and Race Show-Favorable Mail-Answered by Form Letter (Box-folder 64:6)
  - 1963 Aug Television-CBS Press and Race Show-Favorable Mail-Answered by Form Letter (Box-folder 64:7)
  - 1963 Sep, n.d. Television-CBS Press and Race Show-Favorable Mail-Answered by Form Letter (Box-folder 64:8)
- Series IV: Book Manuscripts and Reviews
  - 1957The Lasting South-Author Proofs (Box-folder 65:1)
  - 1957The Lasting South - Galley Proofs (Box-folder 65:2)
  - 1957The Lasting South - Reviews (Box-folder 65:3)
  - 1962The Southern Case for School Segregation (1 of 4) (Box-folder 65:4)
  - 1962The Southern Case for School Segregation (2 of 4) (Box-folder 65:5)
  - 1962The Southern Case for School Segregation (3 of 4) (Box-folder 65:6)
  - 1962The Southern Case for School Segregation (4 of 4) (Box-folder 65:7)
  - [1962] (Bound Volume) U.S. v. The South: A Brief for the Defense-James Jackson Kilpatrick
  - 1962The Southern Case for School Segregation (1 of 3) (Box-folder 66:1)
  - 1962The Southern Case for School Segregation (2 of 3) (Box-folder 66:2)
  - 1962The Southern Case for School Segregation (3 of 3) (Box-folder 66:3)
  - 1963-1964The Southern Case for School Segregation-Correspondence (Box-folder 66:4)
  - 1962The Southern Case for School Segregation-Galley Proofs (Box-folder 66:5)
  - 1962-1963The Southern Case for School Segregation-Reviews (Box-folder 66:6)
  - n.d.The Southern Case for School Segregation-Review Chart (Oversize)
  - 1956The Sovereign States (1 of 5) (Box-folder 67:1)
  - 1956The Sovereign States (2 of 5) (Box-folder 67:2)
  - 1956The Sovereign States (3 of 5) (Box-folder 67:3)
  - 1956The Sovereign States (4 of 5) (Box-folder 67:4)
  - 1956The Sovereign States (5 of 5) (Box-folder 67:5)
  - 1955-1956The Sovereign States - Correspondence (Box-folder 67:6)
  - 1957The Sovereign States - Correspondence (Box-folder 67:7)
  - [1956]The Sovereign States-Components (Dust Jackets, Notes, Revisions, etc.) (Box-folder 67:8)
  - 1956The Sovereign States - Index (Box-folder 68:1)
  - 1956-1957The Sovereign States-Reviews (1 of 2) (Box-folder 68:2)
  - 1956-1957The Sovereign States-Reviews (2 of 2) (Box-folder 68:3)
  - [1960]The Smut Peddlers-(1 of 5) (Box-folder 68:4)
  - [1960]The Smut Peddlers-(2 of 5) (Box-folder 68:5)
  - [1960]The Smut Peddlers-(3 of 5) (Box-folder 68:6)
  - [1960]The Smut Peddlers-(4 of 5) (Box-folder 68:7)
  - [1960]The Smut Peddlers-(5 of 5) (Box-folder 68:8)
  - 1960The Smut Peddlers-(1 of 4) (Box-folder 68:9)
  - 1960The Smut Peddlers-(2 of 4) (Box-folder 68:10)
  - 1960The Smut Peddlers-(3 of 4) (Box-folder 69:1)
  - 1960The Smut Peddlers-(4 of 4) (Box-folder 69:2)
  - 1959-1960The Smut Peddlers-Alias Bank Accounts (Box-folder 69:3)
  - 1959 1960The Smut Peddlers - Correspondence (Box-folder 69:4)
  - 1960The Smut Peddlers - Correspondence (Box-folder 69:5)
  - 1961, n.d.The Smut Peddlers - Correspondence (Box-folder 69:6)
  - 1960-1962The Smut Peddlers - Reviews (Box-folder 69:7)